{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","address":"1331 Trumbull","zipcode":"48216","owner":"Barry Caplan","licenseNumber":"200077","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/13/2017","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E610000058B1F99728C454C0A8F37C2EDC294540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44935","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","inspectionDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"3","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44935","inspectionDate":"1/18/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"2-301.12","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their hands and exposed portions of their arms for at least 20 seconds and thoroughly rinsing with clean water. EMPLOYEES shall pay particular attention to the areas underneath the fingernails and between the fingers. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used common towel","subProblem":"Laying on table/counter","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use."},{"inspectionid":"44935","inspectionDate":"1/18/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on face","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide beard net."},{"inspectionid":"44935","inspectionDate":"1/18/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"44935","inspectionDate":"1/18/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"inspectionid":"44935","inspectionDate":"1/18/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"44935","inspectionDate":"1/18/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"}]},{"inspectionid":"42740","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","inspectionDate":"2018-06-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"0","pfcount":"3","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42740","inspectionDate":"6/25/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"inspectionid":"42740","inspectionDate":"6/25/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"inspectionid":"42740","inspectionDate":"6/25/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"inspectionid":"42740","inspectionDate":"6/25/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"3-602.11","violationDescription":"(A)  FOOD PACKAGED in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, shall be labeled as specified in LAW. \r\n(B) The name of the FOOD source for each MAJOR FOOD ALLERGEN contained in the FOOD unless the FOOD source is already part of the common or usual name of the respective ingredient. (Pf)\r\n(C)  Bulk FOOD that is available for CONSUMER self-dispensing shall be prominently labeled with the following information in plain view of the CONSUMER:\r\n(1)  the manufacturer's or processor's label that was provided with the  FOOD; or \r\n(2)  A card, sign, or other method of notification that includes the information required by law. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food label(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"41034","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","inspectionDate":"2017-12-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41034","inspectionDate":"12/14/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Stove Burners","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"39158","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","inspectionDate":"2017-06-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39158","inspectionDate":"6/23/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Inside the Cooler (salad)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"},{"inspectionid":"39158","inspectionDate":"6/23/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Shelf","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"39158","inspectionDate":"6/23/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Menu","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"39158","inspectionDate":"6/23/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"6-501.113","violationDescription":"Maintenance tools such as brooms, mops, vacuum cleaners, and similar items shall be:\r\n(A) Stored so they do not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; and\r\n(B) Stored in an orderly manner that facilitates cleaning the area used for storing the maintenance tools.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Maintenance tool storage","subItem":"mops","problemDescription":"Unorganized","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"At the Mop","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in an orderly manner."}]},{"inspectionid":"38612","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","inspectionDate":"2017-05-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inspectorid":"122","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38612","inspectionDate":"5/4/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"38612","inspectionDate":"5/4/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"5-203.11","violationDescription":"(A)  A HANDWASHING SINK or an approved automatic handwashing unit shall be provided as necessary for their convenient use by EMPLOYEES in areas specified and not fewer than the number of HANDWASHING SINKS required by LAW shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n(B)  If APPROVED, when FOOD exposure is limited and HANDWASHING SINKS are not conveniently available, such as in some mobile or TEMPORARY FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS or at some VENDING MACHINE LOCATIONS, EMPLOYEES may use chemically treated towelettes for handwashing.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cookline","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"38612","inspectionDate":"5/4/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"wall covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Smooth","location":"BAR","subLocation":"Wall(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"38612","inspectionDate":"5/4/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5174","name":"Red Dunn/ Events","violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Bar","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5174"}}